<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Le Tung Bach, Ph.D.</title>
    <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Le Tung Bach, Ph.D.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://letungbach.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>fb algorithm</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/fb-algorithm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/fb-algorithm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;## Facebook Algorithm Insights for 2025&#xA;&#xA;This document summarizes key insights into the Facebook algorithm for 2025, drawing from the provided sources.&#xA;&#xA;### What is the Facebook Algorithm?&#xA;&#xA;*   The Facebook algorithm uses programming rules and **machine learning to decide what you see in your Facebook Feed**.&#xA;*   It selects posts, Stories, and ads based on your **interactions, the type of content, and how recent the posts are**, aiming to give you a personalized and engaging experience.&#xA;*   The algorithm has transformed into a **sophisticated, AI-driven system focused on delivering content that resonates with users’ preferences**.&#xA;*   Meta acknowledges the algorithm’s imperfections and the possibility that it may never achieve flawlessness, but there’s a clear commitment to evolving and refining its approach to align with user desires.&#xA;*   **Facebook&amp;#39;s algorithm determines what content users see and can greatly affect your posts’ interaction and engagement numbers**.&#xA;*   Understanding these algorithms is crucial for individuals and businesses alike, as it can greatly impact their online presence and success.&#xA;&#xA;### How the Facebook News Feed Algorithm Works in 2025&#xA;&#xA;*   The Facebook algorithm now actively recommends a significant amount of content from sources users haven&amp;#39;t connected with, accounting for **over 20% of content in the Feed**. This marks a transformation into a powerful content discovery engine.&#xA;*   The algorithm increasingly emphasizes &amp;#34;**meaningful interactions**&amp;#34; – actions like thoughtful comments and discussion-provoking shares – rather than just simple likes.&#xA;*   Meta has publicly described the basic process the algorithm uses to rank connected content (from user connections) through four main steps: **Inventory, Signals, Predictions, Score**. This process is widely confirmed across various documents and analyses.&#xA;    *   **Inventory:** The system gathers all potential posts that could be displayed in a user&amp;#39;s Feed since their last login. For connected content, sources include posts from friends, Pages the user follows, and Groups they have joined. Content violating Facebook&amp;#39;s Community Standards is removed at this stage.&#xA;    *   **Signals:** The algorithm considers thousands of &amp;#34;**signals**&amp;#34; – various data points – to assess the relevance and value of each post to the specific user. These signals include information about the poster (relationship to the user, interaction history), characteristics of the post (content type, time posted), and how the user has interacted with similar content in the past.&#xA;    *   **Predictions:** AI powers complex **prediction models (Meta mentions over 100 models for Feed alone)** to calculate relevance scores for each post based on thousands of signals. These models include deep neural networks, attention models, and graph neural networks to capture complex data relationships. Meta uses advanced research models like MViT (for video), XLM-R/XLM-V (for language), FLAVA/Omnivore (multimodal) to understand content across different formats.&#xA;    *   **Score:** Based on the predictions, each post receives a relevance score, and the Feed is ranked accordingly.&#xA;*   Ranking **recommended content** (from unfollowed sources) requires more complex AI systems capable of analyzing vast amounts of content outside the user&amp;#39;s network. These systems predict interests based on overall platform behavior, content semantics, and broader user behavior patterns.&#xA;*   The internal technical reality is a **multi-stage ranking architecture**:&#xA;    *   **Candidate Selection:** Gathering potential posts.&#xA;    *   **Lightweight Filtering:** Quickly narrowing the pool using initial machine learning models.&#xA;    *   **Heavy Scoring (Neural Network Pass):** Deploying more powerful neural network models for detailed prediction scores.&#xA;*   The scale of operation (billions of users, trillions of posts, thousands of signals) necessitates such efficiency.&#xA;&#xA;### How Facebook Recommends Content&#xA;&#xA;*   Facebook’s system for recommending content presents a valuable opportunity for brands and creators to engage new audiences without relying on paid advertising.&#xA;*   No two users will see the same set of recommendations, aligning with Facebook’s objective to provide relevant and valuable recommendations tailored to each individual.&#xA;*   To enhance your content’s likelihood of being recommended, it’s crucial to understand and comply with Facebook’s guidelines and Community Standards.&#xA;*   Facebook actively demotes or removes content considered problematic, including misinformation, fake news, spam, engagement bait, clickbait, low-quality content, sensational health claims, hate speech, etc..&#xA;&#xA;### Content to Avoid&#xA;&#xA;*   **Content compromising safety**, like discussions of self-harm, suicide, eating disorders, sexually explicit material, or promotion of regulated products.&#xA;*   **Sensitive or low-quality content**, such as ‘miracle’ health supplements or questionable financial schemes.&#xA;*   **Disliked content by users**, like clickbait or engagement bait.&#xA;*   **Low-quality publishing**, such as news content lacking transparent authorship.&#xA;*   **False or misleading content**, including fake news or claims debunked by independent fact-checkers, like vaccine misinformation.&#xA;*   **Clickbait**, which typically consists of exaggerated, almost spam-like content that makes over-the-top promises but fails to fulfill them.&#xA;*   **Engagement bait**, which involves using captions or images that explicitly prompt user actions without genuinely enhancing user interaction or providing value. Examples include &amp;#34;Like this post if you are an early bird, share it if you’re a night owl&amp;#34;.&#xA;*   **Reposting content from other sources without adding value** will have limited reach.&#xA;*   Blurry, low-resolution **videos**, those with watermarks from other apps (like TikTok), videos with borders, or horizontal format videos for Reels.&#xA;&#xA;### Tips for Working with Facebook’s Algorithm&#xA;&#xA;*   **Create Relevant Content for Your Target Audience**: Your primary objective should always be to produce high-quality content that truly resonates with your audience. The more relevant and effective your content is, the more likely it is to garner engagement. Use metrics in Facebook Insights to analyze what performs well.&#xA;*   **Don’t Use Clickbait and Engagement Bait**: Facebook frequently updates its algorithm to identify and reduce the reach of such posts.&#xA;*   **Engage Facebook Users and Encourage Interaction**: Interaction plays a significant role in how the Facebook algorithm ranks content. Design your posts to maximize engagement and spark dialogue. Respond to your audience when possible.&#xA;*   **Avoid Spreading Fake News**: Distributing fake news is a violation of Facebook’s Community Standards and can lead to severe consequences, including being banned.&#xA;*   **Post Consistently, but Focus on Quality Over Quantity**.&#xA;*   **Utilize Facebook’s Features** like Stories, Live videos, or Groups to increase engagement.&#xA;*   **Engage with Other Posts and Respond Promptly to Comments**. Facebook suggests replying within 24 hours.&#xA;*   **Understand Your Audience’s Preferences and Behaviors**, using analytics to align your social media strategy.&#xA;*   **Transform Your Best Reviews into Concise Facebook Posts** and tag the individuals who left them to enhance engagement and bring in new followers.&#xA;*   **Create Engaging Video Content**: Facebook offers various video formats, including Reels and Stories (shorter clips), as well as Facebook Videos on Demand and Live videos. Reels has emerged as Facebook’s most rapidly growing content format. Focus on crafting original and authentic videos that embody your brand’s unique voice. Optimize creative elements for mobile users, including vertical format, shorter and impactful text, clear overlays, and concise headlines. **Prioritize short-form videos (Reels) over static posts**.&#xA;*   **Don’t Forget the Basic Status Post**: Simple status posts (without photos, videos, or links) can be excellent for conveying straightforward information and securing high engagement levels.&#xA;*   **Put Ad Dollars Behind Your Most Impactful Content**: Boost or sponsor posts that already perform well organically. Ensure your content is engaging and relevant to your audience.&#xA;*   **Create content that encourages people to share via Messenger** (memes, insightful posts, relatable content). Prompt your audience to send posts to friends or discuss in group chats. **Private sharing (Messenger, WhatsApp, DMs) is now tracked as a ranking factor**.&#xA;*   **Posts that feel thoughtful, genuine, and relevant** are far more likely to get people to pause, react, or share.&#xA;*   Ask yourself, &amp;#34;**Would people share my story with their friends or recommend it to others?**&amp;#34; before publishing.&#xA;*   **Share posts that work on Facebook**: According to a 2024 Meta report, nearly 98% of viewed posts didn’t include a link. Most of what appears in feeds is content viewable without leaving the platform (reels, photos, carousels, text-based posts). Use links selectively and avoid linking to &amp;#34;low-quality web experiences&amp;#34;.&#xA;*   **Publish posts that create meaningful conversations**: Facebook likes authentic accounts that contribute to their community and help start or sustain thoughtful conversations.&#xA;*   The algorithm increasingly shows preference for content that is **authentic and showcases the human side of a brand**. Effective strategies include featuring employees or customers, using real photos, sharing behind-the-scenes content, telling personal stories, and interacting sincerely.&#xA;*   **A notable trend is the algorithm&amp;#39;s increasing prioritization of content shared within Facebook Groups**. Posts within highly engaged Groups now have the potential for better visibility. Active participation in or building relevant Facebook Groups is becoming increasingly important.&#xA;&#xA;### Facebook Not Paying Creators in 2025&#xA;&#xA;*   As of **August 31, 2025, Facebook will no longer offer monetization programs for Reels**, meaning the end of earning from Ads on Reels, In-stream Ads, and Bonus Programs.&#xA;*   Some creators have been experiencing issues with not getting paid by Facebook, even before the announced end of Reels monetization. This includes withheld payments and lack of clear reasons or support.&#xA;*   Despite the discontinuation of some programs, some users are still exploring and discussing ways to monetize their Facebook content in 2025.&#xA;*   There are reports of issues with existing monetization features like In-stream Ads.&#xA;*   Some creators suggest shifting focus from relying on platform monetization to building their own online businesses and promoting digital products.&#xA;*   There are discussions and tutorials about Facebook monetization still existing in 2025.&#xA;*   Facebook has announced a new bonus program for story views.&#xA;&#xA;### Facebook Algorithm Changes and Meta&amp;#39;s Approach&#xA;&#xA;*   In 2025, Facebook&amp;#39;s algorithm updates focus on **AI-driven recommendations, deeper engagement metrics, and a shift toward meaningful interactions**.&#xA;*   Meta is aiming to have the world’s best recommendation technology by the end of 2026.&#xA;*   Meta is moving away from its third-party fact-checking program in the US and moving to a **Community Notes model**, similar to X, where the community decides when posts are potentially misleading and need more context.&#xA;*   Meta will allow **more speech by lifting restrictions on some topics** that are part of mainstream discourse and focusing enforcement on illegal and high-severity violations.&#xA;*   They will take a **more personalized approach to political content**, so that people who want to see more of it in their feeds can.&#xA;*   Meta acknowledges over-enforcing rules and wants to undo the mission creep that has made rules too restrictive. They will rely more on user reports for less severe policy violations and require a much higher degree of confidence before content is taken down.&#xA;&#xA;### Tools for Managing Facebook Content&#xA;&#xA;*   **SocialBee** offers features for content creation, engagement, scheduling &amp;amp; publishing, collaboration, AI assistance, and analytics to help manage social media content. It can help with creating, publishing, analyzing, engaging, and collaborating on Facebook. SocialBee has an Engagement Module and a Social Inbox.&#xA;&#xA;This summary provides an overview of the Facebook algorithm in 2025 based on the provided sources. Remember that algorithms are constantly evolving, so staying updated with the latest insights is crucial.&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hijacking LLM</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/hijacking-llm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/hijacking-llm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Hijacking Large Language Models: Vulnerabilities, Threat Models, Exploits, and Mitigation Strategies&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author:&lt;/strong&gt; Le Tung Bach&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Date:&lt;/strong&gt; March 7, 2025&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Large Language Models (LLMs) are increasingly integrated into diverse applications, making their security and reliability paramount. This research addresses the &lt;strong&gt;importance&lt;/strong&gt; of understanding and mitigating LLM hijacking – malicious manipulation aimed at controlling or corrupting model outputs. Current research often focuses on specific attack vectors, but a holistic understanding, standardized threat modeling, and systematic evaluation of defenses remain a &lt;strong&gt;research gap&lt;/strong&gt;. This paper&amp;rsquo;s &lt;strong&gt;research objectives&lt;/strong&gt; are to: (1) define and categorize LLM hijacking techniques; (2) conduct a comprehensive review of existing vulnerabilities; (3) develop a formal threat model adapted for LLMs; (4) simulate a representative hijacking technique (prompt injection) to demonstrate feasibility; (5) propose and discuss mitigation strategies; and (6) analyze the ethical and policy implications. The &lt;strong&gt;methodology&lt;/strong&gt; combines literature synthesis, theoretical threat modeling (adapting STRIDE), and computational experimentation using a simulated prompt injection attack on a pre-trained LLM (GPT-2 architecture via Hugging Face&amp;rsquo;s &lt;code&gt;transformers&lt;/code&gt;). &lt;strong&gt;Key findings&lt;/strong&gt; demonstrate the ease with which simple prompt injection can override intended instructions in a standard LLM, highlighting significant vulnerabilities. The simulation confirms that carefully crafted adversarial prompts can reliably hijack model output. &lt;strong&gt;Implications&lt;/strong&gt; of this research underscore the urgent need for robust defense mechanisms, standardized security evaluation protocols for LLMs, and proactive policy development to govern their safe deployment, mitigating risks such as misinformation generation, data exfiltration, and unauthorized system interactions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language Programming</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/natural-language-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/natural-language-programming/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;natural-language-programming-evolution-techniques-applications-and-future-directions&#34;&gt;Natural Language Programming: Evolution, Techniques, Applications, and Future Directions&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-introduction-defining-natural-language-programming&#34;&gt;1. Introduction: Defining Natural Language Programming&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Natural Language Programming (NLPg) represents an emerging paradigm aiming to bridge the gap between human language and computer execution. Its core objective is to enable users, including those with limited or no formal programming expertise, to instruct computers or generate code using natural language, such as English.1 This involves translating potentially ambiguous, high-level natural language descriptions into precise, executable instructions or code.2 The ultimate goal is to make programming more intuitive, accessible, and aligned with human thought processes, thereby potentially democratizing software creation and task automation.1&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>market-research</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/market-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/market-research/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;market-opportunities-for-ai-agents-and-multi-ai-agent-systems-in-vietnam&#34;&gt;Market Opportunities for AI Agents and Multi-AI Agent Systems in Vietnam&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-executive-summary&#34;&gt;1. Executive Summary&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape is undergoing a rapid transformation, presenting significant opportunities for the adoption of advanced automation technologies such as AI Agents and Multi-AI Agent systems. This report provides a comprehensive analysis of the Vietnamese market, highlighting the immediate needs across key sectors including travel tourism, real estate, customer service, logistics, and manufacturing. The analysis reveals a strong government commitment to digital transformation and AI development, coupled with a high rate of technology adoption among businesses. While the market for AI Agents and Multi-AI Agent systems is still in its early stages, specific areas like customer service automation, personalized experiences in travel tourism, and efficiency improvements in real estate show immediate promise. This report recommends a phased approach to market entry, initially focusing on these high-potential areas with tailored strategies for marketing, pricing, and customer acquisition, ultimately positioning service providers to capitalize on the transformative power of AI in Vietnam.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAAS</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/multi-ai-agent-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/multi-ai-agent-system/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/tadata-org/fastapi_mcp&#34;&gt;https://github.com/tadata-org/fastapi_mcp&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;A zero-configuration tool for automatically exposing FastAPI endpoints as Model Context Protocol (MCP) tools:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Exposing FastAPI Endpoints as MCP Tools&lt;/strong&gt;:&#xA;- Automatically converts existing FastAPI endpoints into MCP-compatible tools.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;    Preserves request and response schemas, ensuring seamless interaction between APIs and AI systems.&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documentation and Schema Preservation&lt;/strong&gt;:&#xA;Maintains Swagger/OpenAPI documentation for endpoints, making it easier for developers and AI agents to understand and utilize the APIs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flexible Deployment&lt;/strong&gt;:&#xA;Allows mounting the MCP server directly within the FastAPI app or deploying it as a standalone service, catering to different architectural needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Prompts</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/prompts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/prompts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://prompts.chat/&#34;&gt;https://prompts.chat/&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/f/awesome-chatgpt-prompts&#34;&gt;https://github.com/f/awesome-chatgpt-prompts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cookbook.openai.com/examples/gpt4-1_prompting_guide?fbclid=IwY2xjawJss5pleHRuA2FlbQIxMQABHqyv-ZisclOP1ABxgswdYzK-SHBfUS5J_UtyGfxnKYiU8QyNhmOmOEOdGrIX_aem_zKUqHJKSUNhIfMAUmDm1Kg&#34;&gt;openAI4.0 prompting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.norai.fi/courses/prompt-engineering-mastery-from-foundations-to-future/&#34;&gt;https://www.norai.fi/courses/prompt-engineering-mastery-from-foundations-to-future/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;NHIỀU CÔNG CỤ HỌC TẬP ĐƯỢC TẠO RA TỪ VIBE CODING. Vd: app học nhạc chỉ dùng 1 prompt trên Gemini 2.5 Pro trong Google AI Studio.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Prompt: Build a tool to help me learn how music modalities work. Make it interactive and use a keyboard that plays sounds. Include a &amp;lsquo;quiz&amp;rsquo; mode. Make sure the code is in a single file.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(cre: Google AI Devs)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>bookpublishing</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/book-publishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/book-publishing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wikimedia Commons does not provide ISBNs for ebooks or books, as it is primarily a platform for sharing free media files like images, videos, and audio under open licenses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to publish your book and obtain a free ISBN, here are some platforms that can help:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazon Kindle Direct Publishing (KDP)&lt;/strong&gt;: Offers free ISBNs for ebooks and print books. It&amp;rsquo;s a popular choice for self-publishing.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IngramSpark&lt;/strong&gt;: Provides free ISBNs for U.S.-based self-publishers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pencil&lt;/strong&gt;: A self-publishing platform that generates free ISBNs for your book and distributes it globally in ebook and paperback formats.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Draft2Digital&lt;/strong&gt;: A user-friendly platform for publishing ebooks with free ISBNs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These platforms not only provide ISBNs but also help distribute your book to major retailers. Let me know if you&amp;rsquo;d like more details about any of these options!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>emoji submission</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/emoji/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/emoji/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By Vietnamese artist - Itourvn, Public Domain, &lt;a href=&#34;https://commons.wikimedia.org/w/index.php?curid=134955722&#34;&gt;https://commons.wikimedia.org/w/index.php?curid=134955722&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Four_Immortals&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/5/5e/Giong_emoji_Black%26White_original_size.png/120px-Giong_emoji_Black%26White_original_size.png&#34; alt=&#34;Four Immortals - Wikipedia&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanh Giong emoji:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;![[Pasted image 20250410000642.png]]&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://commons.wikimedia.org/w/index.php?title=Special:QrCode&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fcommons.wikimedia.org%2Fw%2Findex.php%3Ftitle%3DSpecial%3AUrlShortener%26url%3Dhttps%253A%252F%252Fcommons.wikimedia.org%252Fwiki%252FSpecial%253AUploadWizard&#34;&gt;https://commons.wikimedia.org/w/index.php?title=Special:QrCode&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fcommons.wikimedia.org%2Fw%2Findex.php%3Ftitle%3DSpecial%3AUrlShortener%26url%3Dhttps%253A%252F%252Fcommons.wikimedia.org%252Fwiki%252FSpecial%253AUploadWizard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[[File:Giong emoji color original size.png|thumb|Thanh Giong (Vietnamese Hero) Saint-Giong emoji color original size]]&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Giong_emoji_color_original_size.png&#34;&gt;https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Giong_emoji_color_original_size.png&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Giong_emoji_color_original_size.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/9/99/Giong_emoji_color_original_size.png/120px-Giong_emoji_color_original_size.png&#34; alt=&#34;Thanh Giong Color Emoji&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://w.wiki/Dkqc&#34;&gt;https://w.wiki/Dkqc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[[File:Giong emoji Gray-scale original size.png|thumb|Thanh Giong (Vietnamese Hero) Saint-Giong Gray-scale emoji original size]]&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Giong_emoji_Gray-scale_original_size.png&#34;&gt;https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Giong_emoji_Gray-scale_original_size.png&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Giong_emoji_Gray-scale_original_size.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/8/87/Giong_emoji_Gray-scale_original_size.png/120px-Giong_emoji_Gray-scale_original_size.png&#34; alt=&#34;Thanh Giong Gray-scale Emoji&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[[File:Giong emoji Black&amp;amp;White original size.png|thumb|Thanh Giong (Vietnamese Hero) Saint-Giong in black and white version]]&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Giong_emoji_Black%26White_original_size.png&#34;&gt;https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Giong_emoji_Black%26White_original_size.png&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Giong_emoji_Black%26White_original_size.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/5/5e/Giong_emoji_Black%26White_original_size.png/120px-Giong_emoji_Black%26White_original_size.png&#34; alt=&#34;Thanh Giong Black &amp;amp; White Emoji&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;![[Pasted image 20250410001306.png]]&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/3.0/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/2/24/CC-BY_icon.svg/120px-CC-BY_icon.svg.png&#34; alt=&#34;Creative Commons License&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New_LLM</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/new-model-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/new-model-introduction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;LLM model introduction&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://allenai.org/blog/olmotrace&#34;&gt;https://allenai.org/blog/olmotrace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Rag</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/self-rag/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/self-rag/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;advancing-agentic-knowledgeable-self-awareness-a-research-agenda-extending-arxiv250403553&#34;&gt;Advancing Agentic Knowledgeable Self-Awareness: A Research Agenda Extending arXiv:2504.03553&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-introduction&#34;&gt;1. Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The development of artificial intelligence (AI) agents capable of complex tasks necessitates mechanisms for robust and efficient knowledge utilization. A critical aspect of this is self-awareness regarding the agent&amp;rsquo;s own knowledge state – understanding what it knows, what it doesn&amp;rsquo;t know, and when external information is required. The paper arXiv:2504.03553 introduces the concept of &amp;ldquo;agentic knowledgeable self-awareness&amp;rdquo; and proposes the &amp;ldquo;KnowSelf&amp;rdquo; method as a novel approach to instill this capability in language agents. KnowSelf utilizes special tokens and a two-stage training process to explicitly signal the agent&amp;rsquo;s perceived knowledge state and guide its information processing strategy (e.g., relying on internal parameters vs. seeking external knowledge).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trend</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/trend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;![[Pasted image 20250413004815.png]]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for tools to track trends beyond Google Trends, here are some great alternatives:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exploding Topics&lt;/strong&gt;: Helps discover emerging trends before they become mainstream. It&amp;rsquo;s ideal for marketers and entrepreneurs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEMrush Trends&lt;/strong&gt;: A comprehensive tool for analyzing industry trends and competitive insights.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BuzzSumo&lt;/strong&gt;: Focuses on social media trends and content performance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pinterest Trends&lt;/strong&gt;: Tracks trending topics and ideas on Pinterest.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trend Hunter&lt;/strong&gt;: A platform for discovering consumer insights and innovation trends.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Treendly&lt;/strong&gt;: Offers trend data across various platforms like Google, YouTube, and Amazon.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keyword Tool&lt;/strong&gt;: Provides keyword trends and search volume data.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TrendWatchers&lt;/strong&gt;: Specializes in YouTube trend tracking.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SparkToro&lt;/strong&gt;: Focuses on audience insights and trending topics.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Muck Rack&lt;/strong&gt;: Tracks trends in journalism and media.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each tool has its unique strengths, so the best choice depends on your specific needs. Let me know if you&amp;rsquo;d like more details about any of these!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethical Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/ethical-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/ethical-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;ethical-intelligence-in-the-era-of-al-navigating-the-post-turing-landscape&#34;&gt;Ethical Intelligence in the Era of Al: Navigating the Post-Turing Landscape&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The rapid advancement of artificial intelligence (Al) has ignited a global conversation about its potential benefits and inherent risks. The unease expressed by authors in London regarding the alleged unauthorized use of their work to train Al models underscores a growing concern within the creative ecosystem. This is not an isolated incident, but rather a symptom of a larger challenge: how to ethically integrate increasingly sophisticated Al into the fabric of our society, particularly within creative and political spheres where human values and rights are paramount. The deployment of Al in support of regimes committing atrocities further amplifies the urgency of establishing ethical boundaries for this powerful technology. It is no longer a question of whether unchecked Al will significantly impact these ecosystems, but rather how quickly and with what consequences. This paper will delve into the concept of &amp;ldquo;Ethical Intelligence&amp;rdquo; in the context of Al that is reaching, and in some interpretations, surpassing human-level conversational abilities, as symbolized by the Turing Test.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>movie</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/movie-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/movie-list/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.phephim.lol/phim-bo/cuoc-doi-duc-phat&#34;&gt;https://www.phephim.lol/phim-bo/cuoc-doi-duc-phat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.msn.com/en-xl/news/other/the-best-movies-about-scientists/ss-BB1r0ilz?ocid=msedgdhp&amp;amp;pc=U531&amp;amp;cvid=9dc942cad2b0487787189f611a1c7a72&amp;amp;ei=15#image=19&#34;&gt;https://www.msn.com/en-xl/news/other/the-best-movies-about-scientists/ss-BB1r0ilz?ocid=msedgdhp&amp;pc=U531&amp;cvid=9dc942cad2b0487787189f611a1c7a72&amp;ei=15#image=19&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/continual-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/continual-learning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;continual-learning-a-review-of-variational-dropout-mixture-of-experts-with-prompting-and-backdoor-attacks&#34;&gt;Continual Learning: A Review of Variational Dropout, Mixture of Experts with Prompting, and Backdoor Attacks&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-introduction&#34;&gt;1. Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The field of machine learning has witnessed significant advancements in recent years, enabling models to achieve remarkable performance on a wide array of tasks. However, a fundamental challenge arises when these models are deployed in dynamic environments where new data or tasks are encountered sequentially. This paradigm, known as continual learning, necessitates the ability of a model to learn from a continuous stream of information without forgetting previously acquired knowledge.1 A major impediment to achieving this goal is catastrophic forgetting, a phenomenon where the learning of new information leads to a drastic decline in performance on previously learned tasks.4 Overcoming this challenge requires specialized techniques that can maintain a delicate balance between the model&amp;rsquo;s capacity to learn new tasks (plasticity) and its ability to retain old knowledge (stability).4&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>get-updated</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/ai-researches-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/ai-researches-updated/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://rss.orbit13.synology.me&#34;&gt;https://rss.orbit13.synology.me&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ai_news_generator&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/patchy631/ai-engineering-hub/tree/main/ai_news_generator&#34;&gt;https://github.com/patchy631/ai-engineering-hub/tree/main/ai_news_generator&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To stay updated on the latest news about AI and neural networks, here are some effective strategies:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google Alerts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Set up Google Alerts for keywords like &amp;ldquo;AI news&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;neural networks.&amp;rdquo; You can choose to receive updates via email or create an RSS feed for your alerts.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RSS Feeds&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use RSS readers like Feedly or Inoreader to subscribe to AI-related blogs, news websites, and research publications. Many platforms, including Google Alerts, allow you to convert alerts into RSS feeds.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tech News Websites&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moe-JEPA vs Titan vs FAN</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/moe-jepa-vs-titan-vs-fan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/moe-jepa-vs-titan-vs-fan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;make a markdown code about the following content:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;comparative-analysis-of-advanced-ai-architectures-fourier-analysis-networks-google-titan-transformer-20-and-moe-jepa-world-models&#34;&gt;Comparative Analysis of Advanced AI Architectures: Fourier Analysis Networks, Google Titan Transformer 2.0, and MoE-JEPA World Models&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The field of artificial intelligence has experienced remarkable evolution with several novel architectures emerging to address the limitations of conventional deep learning approaches. This research provides a comprehensive comparative analysis of three cutting-edge AI architectures: Fourier Analysis Networks (FANs), Google Titan Transformer 2.0, and Mixture of Experts Joint Embedding Predictive Architecture (MoE-JEPA) World Models. Each model employs distinct approaches to overcome current AI limitations, particularly in handling periodic structures, long-term dependencies, and context understanding. Through detailed examination of their architectures, operational mechanisms, advantages, limitations, and empirical performance, this study offers insights into their potential impact on the future trajectory of artificial intelligence research and applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoE-JEPA</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/moe-jepa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/moe-jepa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;research-proposal-moe-jepa-world-models-for-efficient-reinforcement-learning-and-planning&#34;&gt;Research Proposal: MoE-JEPA World Models for Efficient Reinforcement Learning and Planning&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Current AI research emphasizes the development of sophisticated world models capable of understanding complex dynamics, particularly from video data, often leveraging self-supervised learning (SSL) for representation extraction. Predictive models in abstract spaces (like JEPA) are gaining prominence over generative ones. Simultaneously, Mixture of Experts (MoE) offers a way to scale neural network capacity efficiently. This proposal outlines a research approach combining these trends: developing an Action-Conditioned Mixture-of-Experts Joint-Embedding Predictive Architecture (MoE-JEPA) world model. This model will be pre-trained using self-supervision on large video datasets to learn robust visual representations and environment dynamics. The MoE structure will allow the model to efficiently capture diverse or multi-modal dynamics within an environment by routing inputs to specialized expert sub-networks. This sophisticated world model will then be integrated into a model-based Reinforcement Learning (RL) framework to enable efficient planning and decision-making for agents (e.g., robots) interacting with complex environments. We hypothesize that this approach will lead to more accurate world models, improved sample efficiency in RL, and better generalization across tasks compared to monolithic world models.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/apps/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://aistudio.google.com/apps&#34;&gt;https://aistudio.google.com/apps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/dataset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/dataset/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://huggingface.co/datasets/PleIAs/common_corpus&#34;&gt;https://huggingface.co/datasets/PleIAs/common_corpus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kaggle.com/&#34;&gt;Kaggle&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://datacommons.org/&#34;&gt;Data Commons&lt;/a&gt;, but here are some sample data and prompts to try:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://survey.stackoverflow.co/&#34;&gt;Stack Overflow Annual Developer Survey&lt;/a&gt;: try asking “Visualize most popular programming languages”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kaggle.com/datasets/uciml/iris&#34;&gt;Iris Species&lt;/a&gt;: try asking “Calculate and visualize the Pearson, Spearman, and Kendall correlations in this data”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kaggle.com/datasets/uciml/glass/data&#34;&gt;Glass Classification&lt;/a&gt;: try asking “Train a random forest classifier on this dataset”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the largest free datasets available for training large language models (LLMs) is the &lt;strong&gt;Common Corpus&lt;/strong&gt;. It contains approximately &lt;strong&gt;500 billion words&lt;/strong&gt; and is multilingual, covering languages like English, French, German, Spanish, Dutch, and Italian. This dataset is designed to be open and free of copyright concerns, making it ideal for training open and reproducible LLMs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/the-hidden-costs-of-langchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/the-hidden-costs-of-langchain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-hidden-costs-of-langchain-crewai-pydanticai-and-others-why-popular-ai-frameworks-are-failing-production-teams&#34;&gt;The Hidden Costs of LangChain, CrewAI, PydanticAI and Others: Why Popular AI Frameworks Are Failing Production Teams&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1050/0*Vh6rw6R4b2fiyk9a&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After 15 years in software development and countless hours wrestling with AI frameworks, I had reached a breaking point. The promise of “production-ready” AI development tools has become a minefield of abstractions, vendor lock-ins, and overhyped capabilities. Let me share why popular frameworks like LangChain, CrewAI, and even the newer PydanticAI fall short, and why I created Atomic Agents as the solution we actually need.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Agent</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/agent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/agent/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At their core, AI agents are LLMs with a specific role and task that have access to memory and external tools. They use reasoning capabilities to plan steps and take actions to complete tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Four components that make an agent &amp;ldquo;agentic&amp;rdquo;:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;• An LLM (with a defined role and task)&lt;br&gt;&#xA;• Memory systems (both short-term and long-term)&lt;br&gt;&#xA;• Planning capabilities (to determine required steps)&lt;br&gt;&#xA;• Tools (like databases, web search, or APIs)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Agent</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/finetuning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/finetuning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/unslothai/unsloth&#34;&gt;https://github.com/unslothai/unsloth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.unsloth.ai/get-started/unsloth-notebooks&#34;&gt;https://docs.unsloth.ai/get-started/unsloth-notebooks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kaggle.com/code/danielhanchen/kaggle-llama-3-2-1b-3b-unsloth-notebook&#34;&gt;https://www.kaggle.com/code/danielhanchen/kaggle-llama-3-2-1b-3b-unsloth-notebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Google colab&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Agent</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/mvp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/mvp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Viable Product&lt;/strong&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the context of product development, especially when you&amp;rsquo;re talking about guiding AI for screen building (or any software development for that matter), the MVP is the most basic version of your product that has just enough features to be usable by early customers. The goal of an MVP is to gather validated learning about the product and its continued development.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Think of it as the essential core of your idea, stripped down to its most crucial elements. It&amp;rsquo;s not the final, fully featured product, but rather a stepping stone that allows you to:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Cybersecurity</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/ai-cyber/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/ai-cyber/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A Cost-Effective Certification Pathway for AI/LLM Cybersecurity SpecializationI. The AI/LLM Security Frontier: Navigating New Risks and OpportunitiesThe rapid integration of Artificial Intelligence (AI) and Large Language Models (LLMs) across industries presents unprecedented opportunities alongside novel security challenges. Understanding this unique landscape is the first step toward specializing in AI/LLM cybersecurity. This section defines the specific threats targeting these systems, explores the critical role of AI governance, and assesses the burgeoning job market for professionals skilled in this domain.A. Defining the Unique Security Challenges in AI/LLMAI and LLM systems introduce attack surfaces and vulnerabilities distinct from traditional IT environments. Securing these systems requires familiarity with threats specifically targeting the AI lifecycle, from data ingestion and model training to deployment and inference.Key frameworks have emerged to categorize these unique risks:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Dev 25 conference</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/ai-dev-25-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/ai-dev-25-conference/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;c  The AI Dev 25 conference featured extensive discussions on various aspects of AI development, with a strong emphasis on &lt;strong&gt;AI agents&lt;/strong&gt;, their evaluation, deployment, memory management, and interoperability. The importance of moving beyond simple evaluations based on &amp;ldquo;vibes&amp;rdquo; to more data-driven &amp;ldquo;thrive coding&amp;rdquo; using metrics was highlighted. Several open-source tools and frameworks were presented to aid in building and evaluating AI agents, including &lt;strong&gt;Phoenix&lt;/strong&gt; from Arise for evaluation, &lt;strong&gt;Haystack&lt;/strong&gt; for building and deploying agentic workflows, &lt;strong&gt;Llama&lt;/strong&gt; as an open-source large language model, and &lt;strong&gt;Crew AI&lt;/strong&gt; for building autonomous agents.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>benchmark</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/benchmark/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/benchmark/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://gluebenchmark.com/leaderboard&#34;&gt;GLUE Benchmark&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Video generation benchmark&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Vchitect/VBench&#34;&gt;https://github.com/Vchitect/VBench&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2401.01651#:~:text=This%20paper%20introduces%20AIGCBench,%20a%20pioneering%20comprehensive%20and,with%20a%20primary%20focus%20on%20Image-to-Video%20%28I2V%29%20generation.&#34;&gt;AIGCBench&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/NickRiccardi/two-word-test&#34;&gt;https://github.com/NickRiccardi/two-word-test&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://codeforces.com/blog/entry/133874&#34;&gt;https://codeforces.com/blog/entry/133874&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.swebench.com/&#34;&gt;https://www.swebench.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://linzhiqiu.github.io/papers/naturalbench/?fbclid=IwY2xjawJ1xCpleHRuA2FlbQIxMQABHnFZ6hln8p75Kuz4l9F4Mgow7kzEgS1GKuRYj6q-DlvUAWVVRiyVmW1SvnwQ_aem_y_RMPY4cokQHJk8TpxQwpQ&#34;&gt;https://linzhiqiu.github.io/papers/naturalbench/?fbclid=IwY2xjawJ1xCpleHRuA2FlbQIxMQABHnFZ6hln8p75Kuz4l9F4Mgow7kzEgS1GKuRYj6q-DlvUAWVVRiyVmW1SvnwQ_aem_y_RMPY4cokQHJk8TpxQwpQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Baiqi-Li/NaturalBench&#34;&gt;https://github.com/Baiqi-Li/NaturalBench&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;trackingAI.org&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://llm-stats.com/&#34;&gt;https://llm-stats.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://lmarena.ai/?leaderboard&#34;&gt;https://lmarena.ai/?leaderboard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://fiction.live/stories/Fiction-liveBench-Feb-21-2025/oQdzQvKHw8JyXbN87&#34;&gt;https://fiction.live/stories/Fiction-liveBench-Feb-21-2025/oQdzQvKHw8JyXbN87&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://huggingface.co/spaces/adyen/DABstep&#34;&gt;Data Agent Benchmark&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://artificialanalysis.ai/&#34;&gt;https://artificialanalysis.ai/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;LiveCodeBench và SciCode&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://aider.chat/docs/leaderboards/?fbclid=IwY2xjawJs18lleHRuA2FlbQIxMQABHpMzr6OCU0YD65sAyMY5vDd4DKn00s4RKJniEUvlJIIeX4sIYMCtIq7MLZw8_aem_yF2JsBDjLMvkeFDhYfb-6A&#34;&gt;Aider polyglot&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Aider-AI/aider&#34;&gt;github&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://livebench.ai&#34;&gt;https://livebench.ai&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/LiveBench/LiveBench&#34;&gt;https://github.com/LiveBench/LiveBench&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://openrouter.ai/rankings&#34;&gt;https://openrouter.ai/rankings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://arcprize.org/leaderboard?fbclid=IwY2xjawJkGOJleHRuA2FlbQIxMAABHpInxwGwuzaVHnGeNNycEGfhmweu8Xb_aBq5dhGnOHLm1qEbktYZYnqZzNmc_aem_ttSWRTegPXjvOSU1K0DAlg&#34;&gt;https://arcprize.org/leaderboard?fbclid=IwY2xjawJkGOJleHRuA2FlbQIxMAABHpInxwGwuzaVHnGeNNycEGfhmweu8Xb_aBq5dhGnOHLm1qEbktYZYnqZzNmc_aem_ttSWRTegPXjvOSU1K0DAlg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;![[Pasted image 20250410103636.png]]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;EQ-Bench - Longform Creative Writing: &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/2312.06281&#34;&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;![EQ-Bench][https://eqbench.com/images/eqbench3-judge-comparison.png]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://llmbenchmark.kili-technology.com/?_gl=1&#34;&gt;https://llmbenchmark.kili-technology.com/?_gl=1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;1y0re2j&lt;/em&gt;_gcl_au*NzA4OTAwNjM4LjE3NDQ5MjAzNDE.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://eqbench.com/images/eqbench3-judge-comparison.png&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h4&gt;Judge Comparison&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CICD</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/cicd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/cicd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;𝗛𝗼𝘄 𝘁𝗼 𝗰𝗵𝗼𝗼𝘀𝗲 𝗮 𝗰𝗹𝗼𝘂𝗱 𝗖𝗜/𝗖𝗗 𝗽𝗹𝗮𝘁𝗳𝗼𝗿𝗺?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CI and CD stand for 𝗖𝗼𝗻𝘁𝗶𝗻𝘂𝗼𝘂𝘀 𝗜𝗻𝘁𝗲𝗴𝗿𝗮𝘁𝗶𝗼𝗻 𝗮𝗻𝗱 𝗖𝗼𝗻𝘁𝗶𝗻𝘂𝗼𝘂𝘀 𝗗𝗲𝗹𝗶𝘃𝗲𝗿𝘆. In the simplest terms possible, Continuous Integration (CI) is a technique where incremental code changes are reliably and regularly made. Code updates merged into the repository are made reliable by automated build-and-test procedures that CI sparks. Then, the code is swiftly and efficiently deployed as part of the CD process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 𝗖𝗜/𝗖𝗗 𝗽𝗶𝗽𝗲𝗹𝗶𝗻𝗲, as used in the software industry, is the automation that enables developers to reliably transfer incremental code changes from their machines to test and production.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compute</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/compute/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/compute/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;![[Pasted image 20250415204516.png]]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://genk.mediacdn.vn/139269124445442048/2025/4/15/musasdk-4c73590369dcc153a8e01a2db9b79a27-1744699950311-17446999505031306493898.png&#34;&gt;https://genk.mediacdn.vn/139269124445442048/2025/4/15/musasdk-4c73590369dcc153a8e01a2db9b79a27-1744699950311-17446999505031306493898.png&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coworker</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/coworker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/coworker/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Royal unibrew Danish company Ai Staff &amp;amp; manifold.ai&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://theoutpost.ai/news-story/danish-brewer-royal-unibrew-integrates-ai-colleagues-into-human-workforce-14386/&#34;&gt;https://theoutpost.ai/news-story/danish-brewer-royal-unibrew-integrates-ai-colleagues-into-human-workforce-14386/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Royal Unibrew, Denmark&amp;rsquo;s second-largest brewer, has introduced five AI &amp;lsquo;colleagues&amp;rsquo; with names, faces, and email addresses to work alongside their human employees, aiming to enhance productivity and unleash staff potential.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://theoutpost.ai/_next/image/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fcdn.theoutpost.ai%2Ffiles%2Fnews_story_image_14386_238257_d1d185e6f9.jpeg&amp;amp;w=3840&amp;amp;q=20&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;royal-unibrews-ai-integration-a-new-era-of-workplace-collaboration&#34;&gt;Royal Unibrew&amp;rsquo;s AI Integration: A New Era of Workplace Collaboration&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Denmark&amp;rsquo;s Royal Unibrew, the country&amp;rsquo;s second-largest brewer, has taken a bold step into the future of work by introducing five AI &amp;lsquo;colleagues&amp;rsquo; to its human workforce. This innovative approach, developed in partnership with Danish company Manifold AI, aims to enhance productivity and unleash the full potential of its staff &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20250415-danish-brewer-adds-ai-colleagues-to-human-team&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://e.vnexpress.net/news/news/company-gives-ai-names-faces-backstories-even-work-emails-4874382.html&#34;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>inference framework</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/inference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/inference/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/microsoft/BitNet&#34;&gt;https://github.com/microsoft/BitNet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://huggingface.co/microsoft/bitnet-b1.58-2B-4T&#34;&gt;https://huggingface.co/microsoft/bitnet-b1.58-2B-4T&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>kid-link</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/kid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/kid/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;links:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A - lop 4&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSe4IpH3Axe64VFhnO0abz4OR1RiQ6lV7MKXmMIZ9b6Yauc4qg/viewform&#34;&gt;lich su&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdVg8eSEsAuLSkfqSrBIBkytpYAek1cXhD60vzDtiZ8_zLQhw/viewform&#34;&gt;cong nghe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;0 - lop 3&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdRJma4hFJiu7cEZT6rLqu3bK9nRT1qWPij8Bb_qwA-hXtgmw/viewform&#34;&gt;cong nghe&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSeFe3_NS90TZNnGBiZ0av9Ww_kEA0X9hpoAcczFnFgprggVWg/viewform&#34;&gt;tu nhien xa hoi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMtesting</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/test/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.promptfoo.dev/&#34;&gt;https://www.promptfoo.dev/&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/promptfoo/promptfoo&#34;&gt;https://github.com/promptfoo/promptfoo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mcp</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/mcp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/mcp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;opensource MCP:&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/pietrozullo/mcp-use&#34;&gt;https://github.com/pietrozullo/mcp-use&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;![[Pasted image 20250414230045.png]]![[Pasted image 20250414230109.png]]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;![[Pasted image 20250416205343.png]]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;  &amp;ldquo;my-mcp-server-fdbeb09b&amp;rdquo;: {&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;                &amp;ldquo;type&amp;rdquo;: &amp;ldquo;stdio&amp;rdquo;,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;                &amp;ldquo;command&amp;rdquo;: &amp;ldquo;@modelcontextprotocol/docker-mcp&amp;rdquo;,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;                &amp;ldquo;args&amp;rdquo;: []&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;            }&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/quantum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/quantum/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rag</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/rag/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/rag/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://vectorize.io/how-i-finally-got-agentic-rag-to-work-right/&#34;&gt;https://vectorize.io/how-i-finally-got-agentic-rag-to-work-right/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;![[Pasted image 20250414230344.png]]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;![[Pasted image 20250414230302.png]]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;![[Pasted image 20250414230445.png]]&#xA;![[Pasted image 20250414230451.png]]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>reinforcement learning towards AGI</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/rf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/rf/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;reinforcement-learning-charting-the-course-towards-artificial-general-intelligence&#34;&gt;Reinforcement Learning: Charting the Course Towards Artificial General Intelligence&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Reinforcement Learning (RL) has emerged as a pivotal force driving the evolution of modern Artificial Intelligence (AI), offering a paradigm where intelligent agents learn optimal behaviors through dynamic interaction with their environment. Unlike supervised learning, which relies on labeled datasets, RL empowers agents to acquire knowledge and refine their decision-making processes through a continuous cycle of trial and error, guided by rewards and penalties received for their actions. This inherent ability to learn from experience, to explore and exploit the complexities of their surroundings, positions Reinforcement Learning as a potentially transformative pathway towards achieving Artificial General Intelligence (AGI) – the elusive goal of creating machines with human-level cognitive abilities across a wide spectrum of tasks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sitemap</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/sitemap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/sitemap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;sitemap&#34;&gt;Sitemap&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(with anchor link)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[[Home]]&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[[Project A]]&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[[Task 1]]&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[[Task 2]]&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[[Project B]]&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[[Research]]&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;[[Drafts]]&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-dataview&#34; data-lang=&#34;dataview&#34;&gt;table file.name as &amp;#34;Note&amp;#34;&#xA;from &amp;#34;&amp;#34;&#xA;sort file.name asc&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;### 4. **Mind Map Plugins**&#xA;- Install a mind map plugin like &amp;#34;Obsidian Mind Map.&amp;#34;&#xA;- Use it to visualize your notes as a mind map, which can act as a sitemap.&#xA;&#xA;Let me know if you&amp;#39;d like detailed guidance on any of these methods!&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;# Main Subject&#xA;- [Introduction](#introduction)&#xA;- [Section 1: Subtopic 1](#subtopic-1)&#xA;- [Section 2: Subtopic 2](#subtopic-2)&#xA;  - [Subsection 2.1](#subsection-2-1)&#xA;  - [Subsection 2.2](#subsection-2-2)&#xA;- [Conclusion](#conclusion)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;## Introduction&#xA;This is the introduction to the subject.&#xA;&#xA;## Section 1: Subtopic 1&#xA;Details about Subtopic 1.&#xA;&#xA;## Section 2: Subtopic 2&#xA;Information on Subtopic 2.&#xA;&#xA;### Subsection 2.1&#xA;Content for Subsection 2.1.&#xA;&#xA;### Subsection 2.2&#xA;Content for Subsection 2.2.&#xA;&#xA;## Conclusion&#xA;Final thoughts and summary.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;# Table of Contents&#xA;- [Introduction](#introduction)&#xA;- [My Section](#my-section)&#xA;- [Conclusion](#conclusion)&#xA;&#xA;## Introduction&#xA;This is the introduction section.&#xA;&#xA;## My Section&#xA;This is my section.&#xA;&#xA;## Conclusion&#xA;This is the conclusion section.&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>t</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/test1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/test1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;welcome-to-the-agentic-ai-repository-&#34;&gt;&lt;div align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;⚡Welcome to the Agentic AI Repository! ⚡&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This repository is your one-stop resource for mastering Agentic AI, a domain of artificial intelligence that focuses on building autonomous AI agents. From understanding the foundational concepts to building industry-ready AI agents, this repository includes blogs, tutorials, and projects to guide you every step of the way. Let us get started!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;-whats-inside-the-repository&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;✅ What’s inside the repository?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Gain access to resources that cover:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Types of AI agents and their functionalities.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Frameworks for building AI agents like LangChain and more.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Tutorials to build an AI agent from scratch or integrate it with large language models (LLMs).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Hands-on projects to develop your skills in designing and deploying Agentic AI solutions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;-table-of-contents&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;📚 Table of Contents&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;table&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Topics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fundamentals of Agentic AI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Learn the foundational concepts of AI agents, their design, and real-world use cases.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Types of AI Agents&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Overview of various types of agents like simple, goal-based, model-based, etc.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI Agent Frameworks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Explore popular frameworks for building AI agents, including LangChain.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Building AI Agents&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Step-by-step guides to creating AI agents from scratch.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Applications of Agentic AI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Discover how AI agents are being used across industries.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI Agent Projects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Practical projects to get hands-on experience.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;agentic-ai-learning-resources&#34;&gt;Agentic AI Learning Resources&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;-fundamentals-of-agentic-ai&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;📚 Fundamentals of Agentic AI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Discover the basics of AI agents and how they work.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
