<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abtoy on Le Tung Bach, Ph.D.</title>
    <link>https://letungbach.com/tags/abtoy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abtoy on Le Tung Bach, Ph.D.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://letungbach.com/tags/abtoy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Self-Rag</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/self-rag/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/self-rag/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;advancing-agentic-knowledgeable-self-awareness-a-research-agenda-extending-arxiv250403553&#34;&gt;Advancing Agentic Knowledgeable Self-Awareness: A Research Agenda Extending arXiv:2504.03553&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-introduction&#34;&gt;1. Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The development of artificial intelligence (AI) agents capable of complex tasks necessitates mechanisms for robust and efficient knowledge utilization. A critical aspect of this is self-awareness regarding the agent&amp;rsquo;s own knowledge state – understanding what it knows, what it doesn&amp;rsquo;t know, and when external information is required. The paper arXiv:2504.03553 introduces the concept of &amp;ldquo;agentic knowledgeable self-awareness&amp;rdquo; and proposes the &amp;ldquo;KnowSelf&amp;rdquo; method as a novel approach to instill this capability in language agents. KnowSelf utilizes special tokens and a two-stage training process to explicitly signal the agent&amp;rsquo;s perceived knowledge state and guide its information processing strategy (e.g., relying on internal parameters vs. seeking external knowledge).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>get-updated</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/get-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/get-updated/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;yann-lecun-the-future-beyond-generative-ai&#34;&gt;Yann LeCun: The Future Beyond Generative AI&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;12 sources&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The provided transcripts capture various discussions and lectures primarily focusing on the evolution, capabilities, limitations, and societal implications of artificial intelligence and deep learning. &lt;strong&gt;Experts like Geoffrey Hinton, Yann LeCun, and Fei-Fei Li reflect on breakthroughs such as deep neural networks and large language models, including their own significant contributions.&lt;/strong&gt; They discuss the future trajectory of AI research, highlighting the importance of world models, different learning approaches like joint embedding, and the distinctions between human and artificial intelligence. &lt;strong&gt;Concerns surrounding responsible AI development, potential misuse, and the need for open-source platforms are also prominent themes.&lt;/strong&gt; Additionally, personal anecdotes about the speakers&amp;rsquo; journeys and perspectives on the field enrich the content. &lt;strong&gt;The conversations explore both the technical advancements and the broader philosophical and ethical questions raised by increasingly sophisticated AI.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moe-JEPA vs Titan vs FAN</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/moe-jepa-vs-titan-vs-fan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/moe-jepa-vs-titan-vs-fan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;make a markdown code about the following content:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;comparative-analysis-of-advanced-ai-architectures-fourier-analysis-networks-google-titan-transformer-20-and-moe-jepa-world-models&#34;&gt;Comparative Analysis of Advanced AI Architectures: Fourier Analysis Networks, Google Titan Transformer 2.0, and MoE-JEPA World Models&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The field of artificial intelligence has experienced remarkable evolution with several novel architectures emerging to address the limitations of conventional deep learning approaches. This research provides a comprehensive comparative analysis of three cutting-edge AI architectures: Fourier Analysis Networks (FANs), Google Titan Transformer 2.0, and Mixture of Experts Joint Embedding Predictive Architecture (MoE-JEPA) World Models. Each model employs distinct approaches to overcome current AI limitations, particularly in handling periodic structures, long-term dependencies, and context understanding. Through detailed examination of their architectures, operational mechanisms, advantages, limitations, and empirical performance, this study offers insights into their potential impact on the future trajectory of artificial intelligence research and applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
