<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Moe on Le Tung Bach, Ph.D.</title>
    <link>https://letungbach.com/tags/moe/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Moe on Le Tung Bach, Ph.D.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://letungbach.com/tags/moe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>benchmark</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/benchmark/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/benchmark/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://arcprize.org/leaderboard?fbclid=IwY2xjawJkGOJleHRuA2FlbQIxMAABHpInxwGwuzaVHnGeNNycEGfhmweu8Xb_aBq5dhGnOHLm1qEbktYZYnqZzNmc_aem_ttSWRTegPXjvOSU1K0DAlg&#34;&gt;https://arcprize.org/leaderboard?fbclid=IwY2xjawJkGOJleHRuA2FlbQIxMAABHpInxwGwuzaVHnGeNNycEGfhmweu8Xb_aBq5dhGnOHLm1qEbktYZYnqZzNmc_aem_ttSWRTegPXjvOSU1K0DAlg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;![[Pasted image 20250410103636.png]]![[Pasted image 20250410103702.png]]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Rag</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/self-rag/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/self-rag/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;advancing-agentic-knowledgeable-self-awareness-a-research-agenda-extending-arxiv250403553&#34;&gt;Advancing Agentic Knowledgeable Self-Awareness: A Research Agenda Extending arXiv:2504.03553&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-introduction&#34;&gt;1. Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The development of artificial intelligence (AI) agents capable of complex tasks necessitates mechanisms for robust and efficient knowledge utilization. A critical aspect of this is self-awareness regarding the agent&amp;rsquo;s own knowledge state – understanding what it knows, what it doesn&amp;rsquo;t know, and when external information is required. The paper arXiv:2504.03553 introduces the concept of &amp;ldquo;agentic knowledgeable self-awareness&amp;rdquo; and proposes the &amp;ldquo;KnowSelf&amp;rdquo; method as a novel approach to instill this capability in language agents. KnowSelf utilizes special tokens and a two-stage training process to explicitly signal the agent&amp;rsquo;s perceived knowledge state and guide its information processing strategy (e.g., relying on internal parameters vs. seeking external knowledge).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://letungbach.com/posts/continual-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://letungbach.com/posts/continual-learning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;continual-learning-a-review-of-variational-dropout-mixture-of-experts-with-prompting-and-backdoor-attacks&#34;&gt;Continual Learning: A Review of Variational Dropout, Mixture of Experts with Prompting, and Backdoor Attacks&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-introduction&#34;&gt;1. Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The field of machine learning has witnessed significant advancements in recent years, enabling models to achieve remarkable performance on a wide array of tasks. However, a fundamental challenge arises when these models are deployed in dynamic environments where new data or tasks are encountered sequentially. This paradigm, known as continual learning, necessitates the ability of a model to learn from a continuous stream of information without forgetting previously acquired knowledge.1 A major impediment to achieving this goal is catastrophic forgetting, a phenomenon where the learning of new information leads to a drastic decline in performance on previously learned tasks.4 Overcoming this challenge requires specialized techniques that can maintain a delicate balance between the model&amp;rsquo;s capacity to learn new tasks (plasticity) and its ability to retain old knowledge (stability).4&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
